trustarts.org 2019-07-26

# Privacy Policy

**Effective Date: July 24, 2018**

This Privacy Policy applies to your use of the website at www.culturaldistrict.org and its co-branded microsites, such as http://pittsburghclo.culturaldistrict.org (collectively, the "Site") in or on which this Privacy Policy is posted

The Site is operated by or on behalf of the Pittsburgh Cultural District ("Cultural District") and is dedicated to the promotion of Pittsburgh's Cultural District and its member companies: August Wilson Center, Pittsburgh Ballet Theatre, Pittsburgh CLO, The Pittsburgh Cultural Trust, Pittsburgh Opera, Pittsburgh Public Theater, and Pittsburgh Symphony. The terms "we," "our," "ours" and "us" refer to the Cultural District and, as appropriate, one or more Member Organizations.

PLEASE READ THIS PRIVACY POLICY CAREFULLY BEFORE ACCESSING OR USING THE SITE. BY USING THE SITE YOU CONSENT TO THE COLLECTION, USE AND TRANSFER OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION AS DESCRIBED IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH ANY PART OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY, THEN PLEASE DO NOT USE THE SITE.

SCOPE  
This Privacy Policy discloses the information we collect, why we collect it and how we use it. This Privacy Policy does not apply to information that is collected by any third-party websites or services that you may access through the Site.

This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and made a part of our [Terms of Use](https://culturaldistrict.org/terms-and-conditions). If you have not done so already, please also review the [Terms of Use](https://culturaldistrict.org/terms-and-conditions). The [Terms of Use](https://culturaldistrict.org/terms-and-conditions) include provisions that limit our liability to users and other important terms.

INFORMATION THAT WE COLLECT  
In this Privacy Policy, "Personal Information" means information that directly or indirectly identifies you as an individual, such as your name, email address, mailing address and telephone number. "Activity Data" is information that, by itself, does not individually identify you, such as browser type, operating system, the webpages you viewed and how long you viewed them.

We generally do not treat Activity Data as Personal Information. We may, however, link together different types of Activity Data or link Activity Data to Personal Information. If linked information identifies (or can be used to identify) an individual person, we treats the linked information as Personal Information.

HOW WE COLLECT INFORMATION  
We collect information about users that users provide through optional, voluntary submissions to receive electronic newsletters, to submit questions and comments, to share information with a friend, and participation in polls, surveys, and ticket purchases. Some of this information may be Personal Information.

We collect Activity Data when users visit and use the Site, such as such as how long you spend on various webpages, which webpages you view, your search queries, error and performance reports and the webpages that you visited before and after using the Site, as well as Device identifier or IP address, browser type, time zone and language settings and operating system. Activity Data allows us to better tailor content to users' interests and to determine traffic through on the Site. We use cookies, pixel tabs (also known as web beacons, flash cookies and clear GIFs) and similar technology to automatically collect Activity Data.

_Web Beacons_ : A web beacon (also called a pixel tag or clear GIF) is computer code that communicates information from your device to a server. Some of Cultural District’s content and emails may contain embedded web beacons that allow a server to read certain types of information from your Device, allow us to count the number of people who have viewed content, to know when you opened an email message and the IP address of your Device. Web beacons help Cultural District develop statistical information to provide better and more personalized content.

_Cookies_ : Cookies are small text files that are sent to or accessed from your web browser or your computer’s hard drive. A cookie typically contains the name of the domain (internet location) from which the cookie originated, the "lifetime" of the cookie (i.e., when it expires) and a randomly generated unique number or similar identifier. A cookie also may contain information about your computer, such as user settings, browsing history and activities conducted while using the Site.

The Site uses the following cookies: 

  * Strictly necessary cookies, which are required for the operation of the Site. Without them, for example, you would not be able to register or log in for the Site that Cultural District offers.
  * Analytical/performance cookies, which allow Cultural District to recognize and count the number of visitors, learn how visitors navigate the Site and improve the Site.
  * Functionality cookies, which Cultural District uses to recognize you when you return to the Site.
  * Interaction cookies, which allow you to recommend Cultural District on Social Media.

To learn more about web beacons and cookies, visit [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/).

Cultural District also uses analytics services, such as Google Analytics, to collect Activity Data. Generally analytics services do not identify individual users. Many analytics services allow you to opt out of data collection. For example, to learn more about Google Analytics practices and to opt out, visit [www.google.com/settings/ads](https://www.google.com/settings/ads) or by downloading the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on at <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>.

_Your Control of Cookies_ : Some web browsers (including some mobile web browsers) provide settings that allow you to control or reject cookies or to alert you when a cookie is placed on your device. You also may be able to reject mobile device identifiers by activating the appropriate setting on your mobile device. Although you are not required to accept cookies or mobile device identifiers, if you block or reject them, you may not have access to all features available through the Site.

_Do Not Track_ : Some web browsers (including Safari, Internet Explorer, Firefox and Chrome) incorporate a "Do Not Track" ("DNT") or similar feature that signals to websites that a user does not want to have his or her online activity and behavior tracked. If a website that responds to a particular DNT signal receives the DNT signal, the browser can block that website from collecting certain information about the browser’s user. Not all browsers offer a DNT option and DNT signals are not yet uniform. For this reason, many website operators, including Cultural District, do not respond to DNT signals.

HOW INFORMATION IS USED AND SHARED  
Information collected through the Site is used for: 

  * Electronic newsletters: We offer free electronic newsletters. Users may remove themselves from email distribution by following the unsubscribe link provided in every email.
  * "Email a friend" and other social media services: Users can choose to forward Site information to someone else. To do so, the user must provide his or her email address, as well as the email address of the recipient. This information is used only to let the recipient know who sent the email and to send the email.
  * Surveys: We may conduct user surveys to better target our content to our audience. We may share audience feedback and aggregated demographic information with our sponsors, future advertisers and partners. We do not share information about specific individuals with any third party.
  * Donors: Pittsburgh Cultural Trust places a high priority on protecting any financial information that you provide. We do not share or sell any of this information, whether it is obtained online or offline.

Occasionally, we may provide special offers and promotions for non-profit and entertainment organizations to audience members and those that have signed up to receive cultural information. We do not release telephone numbers but may utilize phone blasting technology to inform audience members of vital customer service information such as program changes, weather cancellations, travel advisories, and other event-related news.

We also may use the information we collect from users to (a) provide other services that we may offer or that users may request, (b) assess and measure the use of the Site, and (c) customize and improve the Site and its content.

We share information collected through the Site: 

  * with service providers that help us with payment card processing, sending emails, order fulfillment, conducting advertising, providing customer service or product support, industry benchmarking, consumer analysis, market research and administering promotions.
  * if Cultural District is involved in a merger, reorganization, dissolution, bankruptcy or similar change.
  * if we determine that disclosure of specific information is necessary to comply with the request of a law enforcement or regulatory agency or other legal process;
  * to protect the rights, privacy, property, interests or safety of our company or our affiliates, customers, business partners, employees or the general public;
  * to pursue available remedies or limit the damages;
  * to enforce the Terms of Use or other agreements; and
  * to respond to an emergency.

California Shine the Light Law: California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits users who are California residents to obtain from us once a year, free of charge, a list of third parties to whom we have disclosed personal information (if any) for direct marketing purposes in the preceding calendar year. If you are a California resident and you wish to make such a request, please send an e-mail with "California Privacy Rights" in the subject line to [contact@trustarts.org](mailto:contact@trustarts.org), or write us at: Cultural District Website c/o The Pittsburgh Cultural Trust 803 Liberty Avenue, Pittsburgh, PA 15222

CHILDREN’S PRIVACY  
The Site is not directed to or intended for use by minors. Consistent with the requirements of the U.S. Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act, if we learn that we have received any information directly from a child under age 13 without his or her parent’s verified consent, we will use that information only to respond directly to that child (or his or her parent or legal guardian) to inform the child that he or she cannot use the Site and subsequently will delete that information.

California Minors: While the Site is not intended for anyone under the age of 18, if you are a California resident who is under age 18 and you are unable to remove publicly-available content that you have submitted to us, you may request removal by contacting us at: [contact@trustarts.org](mailto:contact@trustarts.org). When requesting removal, you must be specific about the information you want removed and provide us with specific information, such as the URL for each page where the information was entered, so that we can find it. We are not required to remove any content or information that: (1) federal or state law requires us or a third party to maintain; (2) was not posted by you; (3) is anonymized so that you cannot be identified; (4) you don’t follow our instructions for removing or requesting removal; or (5) you received compensation or other consideration for providing the Content or information. Removal of your content or information from the Site does not ensure complete or comprehensive removal of that content or information from our systems or the systems of our service providers. We are not required to delete the content or information posted by you; our obligations under California law are satisfied so long as we anonymize the content or information or render it invisible to other users and the public.

LINKS  
The Site may include links to other websites, such as Social Media, which are not operated by us. When you click these links, you are navigating away from the Site. A link to a third-party website or digital service does not mean that we endorse it or the quality or accuracy of information presented on it. If you decide to visit a third-party website or digital service, you are subject to its privacy practices and policies, not ours. This Privacy Policy does not apply to any Personal Information that you provide to these other websites and services.

HOW WE PROTECT AND STORE INFORMATION  
Cultural District takes precautions intended to help protect information that we collect and store. Unfortunately, however, no system or electronic data transmission is completely secure. Any transmission is at your own risk and we expect that you will use appropriate security measures to protect your information.

You are responsible for maintaining the security of your account credentials and other authentication involved in obtaining access to password-protected or secure areas of the Site. Cultural District will treat access to the Site through your account credentials as authorized by you. Unauthorized access to password-protected or secure areas is prohibited and may lead to criminal prosecution. We may suspend your use of all or part of the Site without notice if we suspect or detect any breach of security. If you believe that information you provided to us is no longer secure, please notify us immediately using the contact information provided below.

We retain information for as long as necessary to fulfill the purposes for which you provided the information, to comply with law legal obligations, to resolve disputes, to enforce agreements and similar essential purposes.

HOW TO ACCESS AND CORRECT YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION  
If you would like to correct or delete your Personal Information, please send us an e-mail with your request to [contact@trustarts.org](mailto:contact@trustarts.org). Cultural District reserves the right to request that you provide information that will enable Cultural District to confirm that you have the authority to correct or delete the Personal Information that you want corrected or deleted. Cultural District may not be able to correct or delete Personal Information shared with third parties.

NOTICE TO INTERNATIONAL VISITORS  
The Site is operated by Cultural District in the United States but the information that you provide is accessible to affiliates, vendors and suppliers in other countries. If you are visiting the Site from a country other than the United States, your communication with Cultural District will necessarily result in the transfer of information across international boundaries. The level of legal protection for Personal Information is not the same in all countries. If you are using the Site from outside of the United States, by providing your Personal Information to us, you consent to the transfer of your Personal Information to the United States for processing consistent with this Privacy Policy in the United States and in any country to which we may transfer your information in the course of our business operations

CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY  
The Effective Date of this Privacy Policy is set forth at the top of this webpage. We reserve the right to change our Privacy Policy as business needs require. If we make material changes to the way we use Personal Information, we will post a notice about the changes prominently in the Sites. Your continued use of the Site after the Effective Date constitutes your acceptance of the amended Privacy Policy. The amended Privacy Policy supersedes all previous versions.

CONTACT US  
If you have any questions about this website or our privacy policy, please contact us at [contact@trustarts.org](mailto:contact@trustarts.org) or by mail at: Cultural District Website  
c/o The Pittsburgh Cultural Trust  
803 Liberty Avenue  
Pittsburgh, PA 15222  
Box Office: 412-456-6666
